# SEYED MOHAMMAD SHEIKH AHMADI

# **CONTACT INFO**

**E-mail** smsag99@gmail.com , info@sheikh-ahmadi.ir

**Phone** +39 3518371745

Address Turin, Italy

Website sheikh-ahmadi.ir

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a Data Science student at **Politecnico di Torino** and also extremely passionate about programming and research. I founded a firm named VGostar in the Augmented Reality (AR) field at the University of Kurdistan, and also we have been funded by university.

Recently, I have worked in an accelerator firm named **Zharfa** as a back-end developer using Node.js. We were working on some commercial projects.

In 2021, I participated in a research project managed by Dr. Sina Ahmadi from the George Mason University and Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar from the University of Kurdistan. It is supposed to be submitted soon.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# CO-FOUNDER AND BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-2023

**VGostar** | Sanandaj, Iran

• Implementation of AR technology

# JUNIOR BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-Present

**Zharfa Accelerator Academy** | Sanandaj, Iran

MicroLearning Project

## **EDUCATION**

MASTER OF DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2023-PRESENT

**Politecnico di Torino** | Turin, Italy

**BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING** 

2018-2022

**University of Kurdistan** | Sanandaj, Iran

- Accepting and being funded a firm related to AR technology by the university
- Research assistant (RA) and teaching assistant (TA)
- Student Union

## **VOLUNTEER**

#### RA

- Research assistant in **EndoLink** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at the University of Zurich and **Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar** at the University of kurdistan.
- Research assistant in **KurdNet** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at the University of Zurich and **Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar** at the University of kurdistan.

## TA

• Teaching assistant of "Fundamentals of Computer Programming" course with C programming language, with Dr. Amanj Khorramian at the University of kurdistan.

#### STUDENT UNION

Member of IOT student union

## **PROJECTS**

## **MICROLEARNING**

• Back-end of a commercial project at Zharfa Accelerator. source

#### **MEMORAL**

• Desktop Project for selling product in shops and stores. source

# **SKILLS**

Hard Skills • Spark, Hadoop, Pytorch, Java, Python

Node.js , Linux, JacaScript

• Prisma, PostgreSQL, Mongoose, Redis

• Docker-Compose

Familiar with • C, C#, ASP.net

Unity, Arduino, Jekyll, LaTeX

Languages • English IELTS 6.5 (Full professional proficiency)

• Kurdish (Native), Persian (Native)

# **CONFERENCES**

# **EPISODIC MEMORY FOR EGOCENTRIC VISION**

**Politecnico di Torino** | May

• Overview and presentation of a paper named Where is my Wallet

# INTRODUCTION OF MA IN DATA SCIENCE

**University of Kurdistan** | May

Overview and introduction of Master course in Data Science and. Engineering

## **REFERENCES**

Dr. Sina Ahmadi Postdoctoral Researcher University of Zurich sina.ahmadi@uzh.ch

Dr. Amanj Khorramian Assistant Professor University of Kurdistan a.khorramian@uok.ac.ir

Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar Dean of Department of Computer Engineering University of Kurdistan

f.daneshfar@uok.ac.ir